[Music]
My name is Hunter Hogenike and I'm an
associate full stack software engineer.
I am within kind of a DevOps
[Music]
role. So, anything that fails or any
servers that go down, I'm there to help
and support other teams that need my
help. Best part of working on my team, I
think, is the work I'm given. It's uh
very complex, which I do enjoy as a
software engineer, but also very
interesting as well.
[Music]
We generally look for better practices
on how to kind of more effectively work
with other teams and that kind of goes
hand in hand with innovation. We're
always looking for better ideas, better
just applications to build and create
that then again help the entire entire
internal division of manual life. Being
able to see my work in real life helping
others is great. I think what makes Manu
Life a great place to work is the
diversity here and again the support
from everyone. Um, everyone around here
has different experiences and
backgrounds which definitely leads you
to kind of get a better understanding of
whether it's like the software you're
working on or just the business aspects.
Everyone kind of has their own opinion
which is a great way to learn. I think
I'm just looking forward to the growth
of my career here as a new guide. Always
looking for new opportunities to learn
and just soak in as much information as
possible.
[Music]